<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="st_mine_name">
		<text>PFM-1 Scatterable Anti-personnel Mine</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mine_descr">
		<text>A small, air-dispersed mine designed to incapacitate enemy personnel by detonating under pressure (or proximity). Its lightweight design allows for wide-area deployment, making it a persistent hazard in conflict zones.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Proximity\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ied_rpg">
		<text>IED (OG-7V Warhead)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ied_rpg_descr">
		<text>An improvised explosive device utilizing an OG-7V warhead, repurposed to deliver devastating fragmentation effects against personnel and light vehicles. Its makeshift nature allows for concealed placement or remote detonation, making it a dangerous and unpredictable battlefield threat.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Proximity\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ied">
		<text>IED (Chemical)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ied_descr">
		<text>An improvised explosive device designed to disperse hazardous chemical agents upon detonation, creating an area of toxic contamination. Its use poses both immediate and long-term threats, making it a highly dangerous weapon in unconventional warfare.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Proximity\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_balon_gas">
		<text>Gas Balloon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_balon_gas_descr">
		<text>A pressurized metal container filled with compressed gas, primarily used as a portable fuel source for cooking and heating. However, due to its flammable nature, it is sometimes repurposed as an improvised explosive device, making it a potential hazard in conflict zones.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Cooking Fuel\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Impact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_balon_gas_empty">
		<text>Gas Balloon (Empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_balon_gas_empty_descr">
		<text>An empty metal canister that once contained compressed gas, now rendered useless unless refilled. Some traders or technicians may accept it for recycling or repurposing.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Junk\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_metalcan_powder">
		<text>Powder Can</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_metalcan_powder_descr">
		<text>A small and moderately heavy metal canister filled with a mixture of explosive industrial chemicals, metal bolts and nuts as well as black gunpowder retrieved from old ammunition. Upon direct hit, it will instantly explode with metal bolts and corrosive chemicals bursting out in every direction.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Impact\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jerrycan_item">
		<text>Jerrycan</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_jerrycan_fuel">
		<text>Jerrycan</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jerrycan_fuel_descr">
		<text>A large metal canister filled with E95 gasoline. Such fuel is essential for powering vehicles, generators or usable as a high-tier cooking fuel, though some have found alternate ways of utilizing these, namely, as improvised explosives.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Explosive\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Cooking Fuel\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Triggering Mechanism: %c[ui_gray_2]Impact\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_jerrycan_fuel_empty">
		<text>Jerrycan (Empty)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jerrycan_fuel_empty_descr">
		<text>An empty jerrycan that once contained liquid fuel, now rendered useless unless refilled. Some traders or technicians may accept it for recycling or repurposing.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Junk\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
</string_table>