<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<!--
	Overwrites
	fort
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_fort12">
		<text>Fort-12</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort12_descr">
		<text>A semi-automatic pistol designed for military and law enforcement, known for its durability, reliability, and ease of handling. Its ergonomic grip and simple operation make it a practical choice for both professional and civilian users. Widely adopted due to its balance of accuracy and affordability, it remains a staple sidearm in security forces.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Ukraine\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]RPC Fort\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_fort17">
		<text>Fort-17</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort17_descr">
		<text>A modernized polymer-framed pistol offering a lightweight design with enhanced recoil control and improved durability. Built for tactical applications, it features an ambidextrous safety and a high-capacity magazine for increased firepower. Its ergonomic build and low maintenance requirements make it a reliable sidearm for both self-defense and professional use.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Ukraine\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]RPC Fort\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	Overwrites
	fort_snag
-->
	<string id="st_wpn_fort21">
		<text>Fort-21</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_fort21_descr">
		<text>A copy of the Jericho 941 based on the highly regarded CZ-75 short recoil system, the Fort-21 is a high-performance pistol developed for special forces and law enforcement, featuring a modular polymer frame and advanced recoil management. Designed for fast target acquisition, it supports various tactical attachments such as suppressors and optics. Its combination of reliability, low weight, and adaptability makes it an effective sidearm in high-risk scenarios.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Ukraine\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]RPC Fort\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_up_fort21_45acp_name">
		<text>Rechamber to .45 ACP</text>
	</string>

</string_table>