<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

<!--
	ALCOHOL
-->

	<string id="st_vodka">
		<text>Vodka (Nemiroff)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_vodka_descr">
		<text>Nemiroff is a Ukrainian producer of alcoholic beverages, based in the town of Nemyriv in the Vinnytska oblast. Specializing in vodkas and other spirits, they are considered one of the best vodkas in the world and by extension, in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_vodka2">
		<text>Vodka (Putinka)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_vodka2_descr">
		<text>Triple purification, a smooth texture and a unique taste. Following the tradition of naming vodka brands after Russian leaders, Putinka first went into production after Vladimir Putin was elected president. Produced in Russia from the finest grain and crystal clear water from Siberian springs.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_vodka_quality">
		<text>Vodka (Stolichnaya)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_vodka_quality_descr">
		<text>A sturdy metal flask filled with Stolichnaya vodka, often referred to as "Stoli"; a vodka brand with Russian origins, now produced in Latvia. It has a storied history and is known for its classic taste and wide international distribution. Whether used to steady nerves, relax or to celebrate, this iconic Soviet spirit remains a reliable companion in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_beer">
		<text>Beer</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_descr">
		<text>Ukrainian beer encompasses a variety of brews crafted in Ukraine, reflecting the country's rich brewing heritage. These beers range from light lagers to robust ales and are a very popular beverage in the Zone, besides vodka.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_bottle_metal">
		<text>Vodka</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bottle_metal_descr">
		<text>A metal flask containing a portion of what seems to be Zone-produced vodka. While more affordable, the fumes are strong and the quality and taste is lacking, but it gets the job done.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	FOOD
-->

	<string id="st_mint">
		<text>Altoids</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mint_descr">
		<text>Mint-flavored Altoids imported from outside the Zone. While not a meal, they offer a brief respite from the monotony of survival rations. Highly refreshing.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_beans">
		<text>Baked Beans</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beans_descr">
		<text>Canned baked beans in a savory sauce, brought from outside the Zone. This staple offers a comforting taste reminiscent of home, providing sustenance during extended expeditions.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tushonka">
		<text>Beef Tushonka</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tushonka_descr">
		<text>Tushonka is a common name of canned, stewed meat produced in the Soviet Union and other Warsaw Pact countries. It has become a primary means of long-time meat preservation, used both by the civilian population and as a standard-issue Red Army food ration. Tushonka is known for its high nutrition value and relatively good taste.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_bread">
		<text>Bread Loaf</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bread_descr">
		<text>A simple loaf of bread, offering a basic yet essential component of a Stalker's diet. Its versatility makes it a common accompaniment to other food items found in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_conserva">
		<text>Canned Tuna</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_conserva_descr">
		<text>A tin of preserved tuna fish in oil, providing a lightweight and protein-rich meal option. Its compact size makes it convenient for carrying during long treks.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_corn">
		<text>Canned Corn
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_corn_descr">
		<text>Canned sweet corn imported from outside the Zone. It adds variety to a Stalker's otherwise monotonous diet, offering natural sugars for a quick energy boost when needed.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_tomato">
		<text>Canned Tomatoes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomato_descr">
		<text>Canned, sliced and diced tomatoes often used for enhancing the flavor of basic meals. They bring a hint of freshness to the otherwise bland culinary options available.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_chili">
		<text>Chili Beans</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_chili_descr">
		<text>Canned chili beans cooked in a spicy chili sauce. Hardy and delicious, it provides a zesty alternative to standard fare. The added heat can be a morale booster in the cold, desolate environments.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_protein">
		<text>Protein Bar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_protein_descr">
		<text>A compact bar combining the indulgence of chocolate with the nutritional benefits of protein. Ideal for quick consumption, it offers a sweet treat alongside essential nutrients. Useful on longer trips when you're on the go and need to eat something fast.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_kolbasa">
		<text>Doctor's Sausage</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_kolbasa_descr">
		<text>This sausage was originally intended to be a dietary supplement for people exhibiting signs of prolonged starvation. Because it was a mild-tasting, inexpensive and relatively healthy source of meat, Doctor's Sausage became very popular in the USSR. Its extended shelf life make it a practical choice for sustenance in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_nuts">
		<text>Mixed Nuts</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_nuts_descr">
		<text>Assorted peanuts, hazelnuts, cashews and almonds. Offers a dense source of calories and healthy fats. Perfect for snacking on the move, they help maintain energy levels.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_raisins">
		<text>Raisins</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_raisins_descr">
		<text>Dried grapes that serve as a lightweight and natural source of sugars. They provide a quick energy boost and a touch of sweetness to the diet. A good snack to have for the road.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_chocolate">
		<text>Chocolate</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_chocolate_descr">
		<text>A confectionery treat, offering a brief moment of indulgence. While not of premium quality, it satisfies sweet cravings in the bleakness of the Zone. Brings back many fond childhood memories, which may help soothe the pain of living in the harsh and unforgiving conditions of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
    <string id="st_chocolate_p">
		<text>Chocolate (Half-consumed)</text>
	</string>
    <string id="st_chocolate_p_descr">
		<text>Half of a confectionery treat, offering a brief moment of indulgence. While not of premium quality, it satisfies sweet cravings in the bleakness of the Zone. Brings back many fond childhood memories, which may help soothe the pain of living in the harsh and unforgiving conditions of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_salmon">
		<text>Smoked Salmon
		</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_salmon_descr">
		<text>Slices of cured and smoked Ukrainian salmon, delivering a rich and savory flavor. Though a luxury, it provides valuable nutrients and a taste of normalcy.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_sausage">
		<text>Smoked Sausage</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sausage_descr">
		<text>Cured and smoked meat links, packed with robust flavor and protein. Their preservation method ensures longevity, making them a reliable food source in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_breadold">
		<text>Bread Loaf (Stale)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_breadold_descr">
		<text>A loaf of bread that has hardened over time, losing its initial freshness. Despite its texture, it remains edible and can be softened with liquids or used in cooking.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	DRINK
-->

	<string id="st_tea">
		<text>Beard's Tea</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tea_descr">
		<text>Beard's popular hot tea made from a mixture of sugar, edible dried mushrooms and boiled water that is said to be radiation-free. Stalkers who can afford to buy the drink often take it for long trips in the Zone. It's a good and healthy way to stay on your toes when you're getting tired or out exploring on cold nights.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_energy_drink">
		<text>Energy Drink</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_energy_drink_descr">
		<text>A canned beverage featuring an enhanced formula comprised of caffeine, taurine, and vitamins C, B5, B6 and B9. It's often used by Stalkers on long trips due to its sugar and caffeine content or to help sober after one too many alcoholic beverages.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_flask">
		<text>Flask (Clean Water)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_flask_descr">
		<text>A portable flask filled with clean, safe-to-drink water. Essential for quenching thirst without the risk of radiation exposure from contaminated sources.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_mineral_water">
		<text>Mineral Water</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mineral_water_descr">
		<text>A sealed bottle containing calcium-infused carbonated mineral water from Ukrainian springs, rich in essential minerals. Offers a refreshing taste and replenishes vital nutrients lost during strenuous activities.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_water_drink">
		<text>Sparkling Water</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_water_drink_descr">
		<text>Carbonated water stored in a bottle, providing a fizzy alternative to still water. A rare treat in the Zone, offering a momentary escape from the bleakness of daily survival.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_drink_crow">
		<text>Tea "The Beak"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drink_crow_descr">
		<text>"The Beak" is a potent concoction of Zone-distilled vodka and the ground beak of a black male crow that has lived in the Zone for over 15 years, believed to contain enriched proteins capable of cleansing radiation from the body. Despite its rumored restorative properties and the fleeting sensation of euphoria it provides, the drink is notorious for its unpleasant taste.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Drink\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol\n
		</text>
	</string>

<!--
	COMBAT RATIONS
-->

	<string id="st_mre">
		<text>MRE</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mre_descr">
		<text>The Meal, Ready-to-Eat is a self-contained, lightweight field ration originally developed for military personnel, providing a complete meal that requires no cooking. Its durability and convenience make it a favored choice among stalkers navigating the Zone's challenges.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_ration_ru">
		<text>Russian IRP-B Combat Ration</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ration_ru_descr">
		<text>Known as the "Individual Food Ration," this pack offers a full day's worth of nourishment, including canned meats, crackers, and beverage mixes. Designed for Russian forces, its compact and sturdy packaging ensures resilience in harsh conditions.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_ration_ukr">
		<text>Ukrainian Combat Ration</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_ration_ukr_descr">
		<text>This ration pack provides Ukrainian troops with a balanced diet, featuring items like buckwheat porridge with chicken, biscuits, and jams. Its design emphasizes practicality and sustenance, catering to the demands of extended missions in the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Food\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!--
	SMOKE
-->
	
	<string id="st_cigarettes_lucky">
		<text>Cigarettes (Lucky Strike)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigarettes_lucky_descr">
		<text>: A pack of American-made Lucky Strike cigarettes, known for their rich flavor and historical significance. Highly coveted in the Zone, they offer a nostalgic taste of the outside world.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_cigarettes">
		<text>Cigarettes (Marlboro)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigarettes_descr">
		<text>Marlboro cigarettes, with their distinctive red and white packaging, are a symbol of Western smoking culture. Their smooth blend provides a familiar respite for those traversing the Zone's hardships.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_cigarettes_russian">
		<text>Cigarettes (Russian)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigarettes_russian_descr">
		<text>Locally produced, these unbranded Russian cigarettes are widely available and affordable. While lacking the prestige of imported brands, they deliver the necessary nicotine fix for weary stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cigar1">
		<text>Cigarettes (Soviet)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigar1_descr">
		<text>A pack of aged cigarettes produced during the Soviet era, remarkably preserved and still carrying the distinct, harsh flavor reminiscent of the USSR’s golden years. Despite their age, the unique blend of low-grade tobacco and paper filters keeps the signature Soviet taste intact, evoking a sense of nostalgia among older inhabitants of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cigar2">
		<text>Cigarettes (Soviet)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigar2_descr">
		<text>A pack of aged cigarettes produced during the Soviet era, remarkably preserved and still carrying the distinct, harsh flavor reminiscent of the USSR’s golden years. Despite their age, the unique blend of low-grade tobacco and paper filters keeps the signature Soviet taste intact, evoking a sense of nostalgia among older inhabitants of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cigar3">
		<text>Cigarettes (Soviet)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigar3_descr">
		<text>A pack of aged cigarettes produced during the Soviet era, remarkably preserved and still carrying the distinct, harsh flavor reminiscent of the USSR’s golden years. Despite their age, the unique blend of low-grade tobacco and paper filters keeps the signature Soviet taste intact, evoking a sense of nostalgia among older inhabitants of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_cuban_cigar">
		<text>Cuban Cigar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cuban_cigar_descr">
		<text> A luxurious Cuban cigar, renowned for its exceptional craftsmanship and rich, complex flavors. In the Zone, possessing one is a mark of distinction, often reserved for special occasions or significant trades.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_hand_rolling_tobacco">
		<text>Hand-rolling Tobacco</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hand_rolling_tobacco_descr">
		<text>Loose tobacco intended for hand-rolling, offering a customizable smoking experience. Resourceful Stalkers appreciate its versatility, allowing them to roll cigarettes to their preferred size and strength.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_tobacco">
		<text>Russian Tobacco</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tobacco_descr">
		<text>A metal tin containing finely cut Russian tobacco, preserving its freshness in the Zone's harsh conditions. Ideal for those who prefer to roll their own cigarettes or use a pipe, it provides a robust and authentic flavor.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Stimulant\n
		%c[d_green] • %c[pda_white] Alcohol Sobering Effect\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
<!-- UNUSED

	<string id="st_vodka_1_radiated">
		<text>Putinka vodka (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_large_1_radiated">
		<text>Zhigulevskoye beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_large_2_radiated">
		<text>Ochakovo beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_1_radiated">
		<text>Baltika ¹3 beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_2_radiated">
		<text>Slavutich Premium beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_can_1_radiated">
		<text>Pripyat beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beer_can_2_radiated">
		<text>Heineken beer (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_water_large_1_radiated">
		<text>Naroch mineral water (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_water_large_2_radiated">
		<text>Leninad mineral water (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_water_can_1_radiated">
		<text>Purified water (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_water_can_2_radiated">
		<text>Mineral water (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cocacola_radiated">
		<text>Coca-Cola (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_redbull_radiated">
		<text>Redbull energy drink</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_guru_radiated">
		<text>GURU energy drink (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_marlboro_radiated">
		<text>Marlboro cigarettes (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_lucky_radiated">
		<text>Lucky Strike cigarettes (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cuban_radiated">
		<text>Cuban cigars (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cigarettes_1_radiated">
		<text>Cuban cigars (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wild_drink_radiated">
		<text>Zone-produced liquor (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_kolbasa_smoked_radiated">
		<text>Smoked sausage (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beanz_radiated">
		<text>Baked beans (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_tomatoes_radiated">
		<text>Tomatoes (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_chocolatebar_radiated">
		<text>Chocolate protein bar (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_snickers_radiated">
		<text>Snickers (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mars_radiated">
		<text>Mars (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_nuts_2_radiated">
		<text>Trail mix (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_beef_radiated">
		<text>Tushenka (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bullheads_radiated">
		<text>Pasta and meatballs (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_sardina_radiated">
		<text>"Pirate" Sardines (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_olivki_radiated">
		<text>Olives (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cheese_radiated">
		<text>"Yantar" processed cheese (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_galet_radiated">
		<text>Biscuits (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_shokolad_radiated">
		<text>"Aljinushka" chocolate (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batonchik_radiated">
		<text>Chocolate bar (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_jerky_radiated">
		<text>Beef jerky (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_chips_radiated">
		<text>Potato chips (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_hash_radiated">
		<text>Biscuits and hash (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cpcb_radiated">
		<text>Salted crackers (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_juice_radiated">
		<text>Orange juice (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mre_1_3_radiated">
		<text>Army MRE (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mre_1_2_radiated">
		<text>Army MRE (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mre_1_1_radiated">
		<text>Army MRE (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bandage_israeli_radiated">
		<text>Bandage (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_amphetamines_4_radiated">
		<text>Amphetamine (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_amphetamines_3_radiated">
		<text>Amphetamine (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_amphetamines_2_radiated">
		<text>Amphetamine (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_amphetamines_1_radiated">
		<text>Amphetamine (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_diazepam_radiated">
		<text>Diazepam (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_psy_complex_radiated">
		<text>Psychodelin (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bio_bandage_radiated">
		<text>Special bandage (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_engine_radiated">
		<text>Anti-hallucinogen (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_drug_cat_eye_radiated">
		<text>Cat's eye (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medo_radiated">
		<text>Moonshine (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_mbk_radiated">
		<text>Caffeine pills (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_medkit_elite_radiated">
		<text>Elite medkit (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bag_medkit_1_radiated">
		<text>Basic medkit (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bag_medkit_2_radiated">
		<text>Army medkit (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bag_medkit_3_radiated">
		<text>Scientific medkit (irradiated)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_bag_medkit_4_radiated">
		<text>Special medkit (irradiated)</text>
	</string>

-->

</string_table>
