<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="st_matches">
		<text>Firestarter Set</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_matches_descr">
		<text>A simple set of pine wood, impregnated with resin. The firestarter set allows creating a small but steady hearth fire. Easy to light, even when wet!\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Use: %c[ui_gray_2]Start Fire\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wood_stove">
		<text>Hexagonal Wood Stove</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wood_stove_descr">
		<text>This compact foldable oven is intended for cooking single entree meals with dry wood. The stove can produce temperatures sufficient to grill less poisoned mutant meat, but preparing more toxic meat requires the utilization of more advanced equipment.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Fuel: %c[ui_gray_2]Charcoal\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Cooks: %c[ui_gray_2]Only Lesser Mutant Meat\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_cooking">
		<text>Field Cooking Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_cooking_descr">
		<text>A kit containing cooking accessories and utensils for use when camping and travelling. Unwieldy due to its heavy weight but still very popular among groups of stalkers. The Cooking Kit can produce temperatures sufficient to grill less poisoned mutant meat, but preparing more toxic meat requires the utilization of more advanced equipment.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Fuel: %c[ui_gray_2]Charcoal\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Cooks: %c[ui_gray_2]Only Lesser Mutant Meat\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_army_bowler">
		<text>Army Kettle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_army_bowler_descr">
		<text>A durable, metal kettle designed for military use, ideal for boiling water and preparing simple meals over a portable heat source. Its robust construction ensures reliability. Comes with a tablespoon inserted into a special hole on the handle.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Fuel: %c[ui_gray_2]Charcoal\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Cooks: %c[ui_gray_2]Only Lesser Mutant Meat\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_fieldcooker">
		<text>Gas Stove</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fieldcooker_descr">
		<text>To be used exclusively with commonly found fuels within the Zone, this stove can cook up anything you throw at it. Unfortunately, these fuels are usually carried in heavy metal containers, making this stove more suited for use at bases, rather than out in the field.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Fuel: %c[ui_gray_2]Gasoline, Jerrycan, Kerosene\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Cooks: %c[ui_gray_2]All Mutant Meat\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_box_matches">
		<text>Matchbox</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_box_matches_descr">
		<text>A small container holding a collection of matches, indispensable for igniting fires in the absence of modern lighters. In the Zone, a reliable matchbox is a lifeline for warmth and cooking.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Use: %c[ui_gray_2]Start Fire, Light Cigarettes\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_kerosene">
		<text>Kerosene</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_kerosene_descr">
		<text>A flammable liquid commonly used as fuel for portable stoves and lamps, providing a reliable heat source for cooking and warmth. In the Zone, stalkers utilize kerosene with multi-fuel stoves to prepare meals safely, as it burns cleaner than contaminated local materials.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Cooking Fuel\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_charcoal">
		<text>Charcoal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_charcoal_descr">
		<text>Compressed carbon material commonly used as a fuel source for cooking and heating. In the Zone, charcoal is preferred over contaminated natural wood, providing a safer and consistent heat source for stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Cooking Fuel\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_fuel_tier_1">
		<text>All Flammables</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fuel_tier_1_desc">
		<text>%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Campfire\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Charcoal\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Gas Balloon\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Jerrycan\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Kerosene\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_fuel_tier_2">
		<text>Liquid Fuel Only</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_fuel_tier_2_desc">
		<text>%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Kerosene\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Jerrycan\n
		%c[d_blue] • %c[pda_white] Gas Balloon\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>
