<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>

<!--
	Devices
-->

<string_table>

	<string id="st_pda_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_descr">
		<text>A Personal Digital Assistant (PDA) serves as a stalker's primary tool for navigation and communication within the Zone. Equipped with maps, mission logs, and messaging capabilities, it helps in coordinating activities and tracking objectives. Its compact design ensures portability, making it indispensable for daily operations.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_1_name">
		<text>PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_1_descr">
		<text>A Personal Digital Assistant (PDA) serves as a stalker's primary tool for navigation and communication within the Zone. Equipped with maps, mission logs, and messaging capabilities, it helps in coordinating activities and tracking objectives. Its compact design ensures portability, making it indispensable for daily operations.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_2_name">
		<text>PDA v2.0 KilTrak™</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_2_descr">
		<text>A Personal Digital Assistant (PDA) serves as a stalker's primary tool for navigation and communication within the Zone. Equipped with maps, mission logs, and messaging capabilities, it helps in coordinating activities and tracking objectives. Its compact design ensures portability, making it indispensable for daily operations.\nThis model comes with a pirated version of the IMI KilTrak software, making it a compelling find among stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Shows Eliminated Target Locations\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_pda_3_name">
		<text>PDA v3.1</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_pda_3_descr">
		<text>A Personal Digital Assistant (PDA) serves as a stalker's primary tool for navigation and communication within the Zone. Equipped with maps, mission logs, and messaging capabilities, it helps in coordinating activities and tracking objectives. Its compact design ensures portability, making it indispensable for daily operations.\nThis model has been greatly improved to retrieve and process the position of other modules connected to the network though it requires a set of codes to acquire higher functions, such as built-in special privileges.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Shows Nearby Neutral Squads\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector1">
		<text>Echo Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector1_descr">
		<text>A basic and dated artifact detection device, utilizing outdated electronics to identify anomalies. It emits auditory signals that increase in frequency as the user approaches an artifact. While affordable, its limited range and functionality make it suitable primarily for novice stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[pda_white] Tier I\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Detects Common Artefacts\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector2">
		<text>Bear Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector2_descr">
		<text>An improved first-generation artifact detector, the Bear Detector features a user-friendly radar display and upgraded electronic components. It provides directional cues, assisting stalkers in pinpointing artifact locations with greater accuracy. This device is favored for its balance between functionality and accessibility.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[pda_white] Tier II\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Detects Common &amp; Rare Artefacts\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector3">
		<text>Veles Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector3_descr">
		<text>The Veles Detector is an advanced second-generation device renowned for its efficiency and reliability. It offers a detailed visual interface, displaying both artifact and anomaly positions, thereby enhancing safety during expeditions. Its higher cost reflects its superior performance, making it a preferred choice among experienced stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[pda_white] Tier III\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Detects All Artefacts\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector4">
		<text>Svarog Detector</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector4_descr">
		<text>As a prototype anomaly and artifact detector, the Svarog Detector represents the pinnacle of detection technology in the Zone. It not only locates artifacts but also maps out static anomalous zones, providing comprehensive situational awareness. Its sophisticated design and functionality make it an invaluable tool for scientific expeditions and high-risk artifact retrieval missions.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[pda_white] • %c[pda_white] Tier IV\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Detects All Artefacts Including Scientifically Unknown Artefacts\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector9">
		<text>RF Receiver</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector9_descr">
		<text>The Radio Frequency (RF) Receiver is a device used to intercept and monitor communications within the Zone. It allows stalkers to eavesdrop on various transmissions, potentially gaining valuable intelligence on faction movements or hidden stashes. Its effectiveness depends on signal strength and the user's proximity to transmission sources.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_detector8">
		<text>Anomalous Measurement Device</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_detector8_descr">
		<text>A device used to take and record measurements of anomalous fields. Its improved framework and high sensitivity sensors, guarantee reliable operation even in the most hostile environments. The first prototype was designed in 2008 under Professor Sakharov's supervision in the Yantar mobile lab. Since then, more copies have been made after its proven success in field study.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Detects Anomaly Locations\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_broken_pda">
		<text>Broken PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_broken_pda_descr">
		<text>A malfunctioning or damaged Personal Digital Assistant, often found discarded or on fallen stalkers. While non-functional in its current state, it may contain salvageable data or components.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Junk\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_name">
		<text>Headlamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_descr">
		<text>A wearable light source affixed to a stalker's headgear; the headlamp provides hands-free illumination in dark environments. Essential for nighttime operations or exploring unlit interiors, it enhances visibility while keeping the user's hands free for other tasks.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_1_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ 1PN93-1 Night Vision</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_1_descr">
		<text>A wearable light source affixed to a stalker's headgear; the headlamp provides hands-free illumination in dark environments. Essential for nighttime operations or exploring unlit interiors, it enhances visibility while keeping the user's hands free for other tasks.\nThis model features a 1PN93-1 night vision device, offering generation 2+ image intensification making it especially useful for operations at night or in low-light conditions.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_2_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ PN21KL Night Vision</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_2_descr">
		<text>A wearable light source affixed to a stalker's headgear; the headlamp provides hands-free illumination in dark environments. Essential for nighttime operations or exploring unlit interiors, it enhances visibility while keeping the user's hands free for other tasks.\nThis model features a PN21KL night vision device, offering generation 2+ image intensification making it especially useful for operations at night under natural illumination and in complete darkness with the infrared illuminator.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_3_name">
		<text>Headlamp w/ Oracle Psi-stimulator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_torch_nv_3_descr">
		<text>A wearable light source affixed to a stalker's headgear; the headlamp provides hands-free illumination in dark environments. Essential for nighttime operations or exploring unlit interiors, it enhances visibility while keeping the user's hands free for other tasks.\nThis model features image-processing software that removes video noise and enhances image-intensifying capabilities of PN21K units, thus making it a full-fledged IIT generation 3+ night vision device.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_device_flashlight">
		<text>Flashlight</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_device_flashlight_descr">
		<text>A handheld portable light source, the flashlight is a staple in every stalker's inventory. It offers focused illumination, useful for inspecting specific areas or signaling others. While effective, it occupies one hand, which can be a limitation during certain activities.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_dead">
		<text>Old Batteries</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_dead_descr">
		<text>Discarded batteries, the outer layer of which is corroded and covered in dirt. In the resource-scarce environment of the Zone, even drained batteries could be useful, as they can sometimes be recharged or repurposed.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Junk\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries">
		<text>Battery Pack</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_descr">
		<text>An indispensable power source within the Zone. Often used for a variety of portable electronic devices, stalkers rely on these energy cells to operate essential equipment such as flashlights, headlamps, and handheld detectors. Remember to keep a few spares in case of an emergency.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Energy Source\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell">
		<text>Military Battery Unit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_batteries_ccell_descr">
		<text>A robust and high-capacity power source used primarily for military-grade equipment. Designed to withstand harsh conditions, these units provide reliable energy for advanced weaponry and communication devices. Often supplied to traders by corrupt military officers trying to earn some extra cash in the Zone, their scarcity makes them valuable commodities among stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Energy Source\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_geiger_dead">
		<text>Geiger Counter</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_geiger_dead_descr">
		<text>A handheld device that measures ionizing radiation levels, the Geiger Counter is indispensable for detecting radioactive hazards. It alerts users to dangerous areas, allowing them to navigate the Zone more safely. Regular monitoring helps in avoiding prolonged exposure to harmful radiation.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_orange] • %c[pda_white] Measures Radioactive Contamination\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_electric power">
		<text>Universal Power Device (Electric)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_electric power_descr">
		<text>A Cold War era power unit about the size of a small walkie-talkie. The device accepts almost any type of battery, utilizing the energy and supplying electronic devices with power in an enhanced stream through a set of micro wires. These wires can be connected to any piece of equipment, regardless of its complexity or age, allowing Stalkers to use and handle numerous electronic devices, even if they have only one battery available.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[ui_gray_2] portable energy source\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="extension_pda">
		<text>Multimedia PDA</text>
	</string>
	<string id="exten_sion_pda">
		<text>An upgraded version of the standard PDA, the Multimedia PDA offers enhanced features such as audio and video playback. It supports a broader range of applications, including data analysis tools and advanced communication interfaces. This versatility makes it a valuable asset for tech-savvy stalkers.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_gps_tracker">
		<text>Military GPS Module</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gps_tracker_descr">
		<text>A prototype of a next generation GPS navigation device, only a few of which exist. Although distributed exclusively among the highest military ranks, some have found their way into the hands of other parties. This module, featuring an improved framework and high sensitivity sensors, guarantees reliable operation even in the most hostile environments. Unlike usual GPS modules, this one relies on sets of codes that allow it to acquire special privileges on the connected network.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_musicplayer">
		<text>Radio</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_musicplayer_desc">
		<text>A modified radio, designed to communicate with other radios, filtering out as much interference as possible. These enhancements facilitate better communication and information gathering within the Zone.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_weather_radar">
		<text>Doppler Weather Radar Kit</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_weather_radar_descr">
		<text>A portable system designed to monitor atmospheric conditions, providing real-time data on weather patterns. This model has been modified and is powered by a 'Meatchunk' artefact. Considered a miracle in the meteorology field, it sends directional pulses of microwave radiation to collect weather data.\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_dosimeter_mode">
		<text>Dosimeter Mode</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_actor_rads">
		<text>Body Radiation</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_environment_rads">
		<text>Environmental Radiation</text>
	</string>

</string_table>