<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<string id="st_wpn_adar2_15">
		<text>ADAR 2-15</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_adar2_15_descr">
		<text>A civilian semi-automatic rifle produced in Russia, heavily based on the AR-15 platform. Known for its precision and lightweight design, it uses wooden furniture and is chambered in 5.56x45mm NATO. Its combination of modern performance and traditional aesthetics makes it popular among sport shooters and civilian firearms enthusiasts.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russia\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Molot Oruzhie\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_siber">
		<text>PKP Pecheneg</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkp_siber_descr">
		<text>A modernized Russian general-purpose machine gun derived from the PKM, designed to provide sustained fire with improved barrel cooling for extended use. It retains the 7.62x54mmR caliber and belt-fed system but incorporates a fixed, non-replaceable barrel with enhanced heat dissipation. Widely used by Russian forces, the Pecheneg is valued for its durability, reliability, and adaptability in both defensive and offensive roles.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Russian\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Mikhail Kalashnikov\n
		</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_siber">
		<text>PKM</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_siber_descr">
		<text>A classic Soviet-era general-purpose machine gun chambered in 7.62x54mmR, renowned for its ruggedness, simplicity, and reliability in combat. Designed in the 1960s, it remains in service with military forces around the world due to its lightweight design for its class and ease of maintenance. Its belt-fed system and adaptability make it effective in a wide range of roles, from infantry support to vehicle-mounted operations.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zenit_siber">
		<text>PKM "Zenit"</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_wpn_pkm_zenit_siber_descr">
		<text>A classic Soviet-era general-purpose machine gun chambered in 7.62x54mmR, renowned for its ruggedness, simplicity, and reliability in combat. Designed in the 1960s, it remains in service with military forces around the world due to its lightweight design for its class and ease of maintenance. Its belt-fed system and adaptability make it effective in a wide range of roles, from infantry support to vehicle-mounted operations.\nThis model has been extensively modified with a Picatinny rail, vertical foregrip, muzzle brake, and laser designator, along with internal modifications to increase weapon fire rate.\n \n
		%c[pda_white]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Origin: %c[ui_gray_2]Soviet Union\n
		%c[d_cyan] • %c[pda_white] Manufacturer: %c[ui_gray_2]TsNIITochMash, Degtyaryov Plant\n
		</text>
	</string>

</string_table>